<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
  <LocalizedText>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_ARCH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
      <Text> A Triumphal Arch is a large Arch with one or more arched passageways.It is often found spanning roads and in it's simplest form consists of two piers connectect by an arch with a flat entablature on which a statue might be mounted or which bears commemrative inscriptions.
      It is often associated with ancient rome but examples can be found all across the world including the Wellingtion Arch (Marble Arch) in London and the Arch de Triomphe in Paris. </Text>
    </Row>
  <!--Civilizations/Leaders -->
    <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ITALY_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Italy</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_LEADER_ALBION_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Albion Lombard</Text>
    </Row>
   <!--Traits -->
   <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_LUXURYTRADE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Bounty of Luxuries</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_LUXURYTRADE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>All Luxuries owned by Italy spread to 4 more cities than usual.</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ARCH_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Triumphal Arch</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ARCH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>The Triumphal Arch replaces the monument.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_GRANDSQUARE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Grand Square</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_GRANDSQUARE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>The Grand Square replaces the Amphitheater and provides gold from the markets held there.</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_CONDOTTIERI_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Condottieri</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_CONDOTTIERI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>The Condottieri are a stronger version of the Knight.</Text>
    </Row>
	<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_CONDOTTIERI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
	<Text>Condottieri were the leaders of well organised mercenaries in Italy. Their code of military justice imposed discipline and called for an equal division of each contract. They were the first to view warfare from the perspective of military science which led to a depature from chivalry.</Text>
	</Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_KINGALBION_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>King of the Lombards</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_KINGALBION_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Gains an additional wildcard government slot.</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ITALY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Italian Civilization</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_ALBION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>
      Greetings oh mighty Albion. You have led the Lombards to found what will become modern Italy. Can you now expand your borders to form a civilzation to compare to the Roman Empire before you? Can you hold together your coalition of forces and conquer other lands? Or will you seek to form a society based upon culture rather than the sword?
     </Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALBION_TITLE" Language="en_US">
	<Text>King Albion Lombard</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALBION_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
	<Text>Leader of the Lombards</Text>
    </Row>			
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALBION_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
	<Text>
  Albion was king of the Lombards. During his reign the Lombards ended their migrations by settling in Italy, the northern part of which Alboin conquered. Albion was later assasinated by the Byzantines in a coup d'etat organised by Helmichis, his foster brother who was supported by Albion's wife Rosamund. Most of the Lombards opposed this and it failed.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ITALY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
	<Text>
  In 568 AD Albion, a young leader of the Lombards, led the Lombard migration into Italy. At least 20,000 Saxon warriors joined them with their families. The first city to fall was Forum Iulii in 569 AD. Verona, Vicenza and Bresica soon followed. Milan fell to the Lombards in the summer of 569 AD as the small Byzantine army guarding it could do nothing to prevent it. They continued to conquer further south. At it's height the Lombard territory was divided into 36 duchies, whose leaders settled in the major cities of each duchy. However this subdivision led to weakness. After the assaination of Albion and his successor Celph there was a period known as the Rule of Dukes when no King was elected until 584 AD.
  </Text>
    </Row>
  </LocalizedText>
</GameData>
