<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v2004 rel. 2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by Ed Beach (Firaxis Games) -->
<GameData>
  <LocalizedText>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_ARCH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A Stele is a large, upright slab of stone or wood used as a monument to commemorate great leaders, victories in battle, or occasionally to mark territorial boundaries. Found throughout Ethiopia and the surrounding regions, the stelae were often intricately inscribed with the details of the person or event being memorialized. The Obelisk of Axum, one such stele, was constructed in the mid-4th century AD in the Ethiopian city of Axum, but was later broken down and shipped to Italy during the occupation of Ethiopia by Mussolini's forces. Standing over 75 feet tall and weighing 150 tons, the great stele was returned to Ethiopia and reassembled in 2008 as part of an effort by the United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization.</Text>
    </Row>
  <!--Civilizations/Leaders -->
    <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ITALY_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Italy</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_LEADER_ALBION_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Albion Lombard</Text>
    </Row>
   <!--Traits -->
   <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_SOUK_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Souks of Ta-Netjer</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_SOUK_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Floodplains do not block placement of commercial hubs, which are provided with an adjacency bonus from all floodplain and oasis tiles. +1 [ICON_Gold] gold for each city following Punt's religion.</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ARCH_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Arch</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ARCH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Monument replacement which grants double the [ICON_Culture] culture output as the monument</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_WORKER_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Worker</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_UNIT_WORKER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>The worker has an extra charge than the builder it replaces</Text>
    </Row>
	<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_WORKER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
	<Text>To survive, a civilization needs skilled workers. They may be highly trained engineers, or civilians conscripted into labour - or, indeed, slaves - but someone has to dig the mines, plant the fields and pave the roads. Without these men and women, a civilization will stagnate and eventually fall prey to a more vigorous neighbour.</Text>
	</Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_PWENET_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Queen of Pwenet</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_PWENET_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Gains an additional economic government slot. Incoming trade routes from other civilizations provide +2 [ICON_Gold] gold for the Punt.</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ITALY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Punt Civilization</Text>
    </Row>
   <Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_ALBION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>
      Greetings oh mighty Albion. You have led the Lombards to found what will become modern Italy. Can you now expand your borders to form a civilzation to compare to the Roman Empire before you? Can you hold together your coalition of forces and conquer other lands? Or will you seek to form a society based upon culture rather than the sword?
     </Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALBION_TITLE" Language="en_US">
	<Text>King Albion Lombard</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALBION_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
	<Text>Leader of the Lombards</Text>
    </Row>			
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALBION_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
	<Text>
  Albion was king of the Lombards. During his reign the Lombards ended their migrations by settling in Italy, the northern part of which Alboin conquered. Albion was later assasinated by the Byzantines in a coup d'etat organised by his Helmichis, his foster brother who was supported by Albion's wife Rosamund. Most of the Lombards opposed this and it failed.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_ITALY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
	<Text>
  TODO
  </Text>
    </Row>
  </LocalizedText>
</GameData>
